You're here, Sis
Tell Lewes to talk to the police
This is a family matter
Let me go
Or Mom and Dad will never forgive you
Mom and Dad can't protect you anymore
They drank pesticide
They're still in the hospital
The doctor said they might not wake up
You're lying to me
That bottle was just water, no drug
It was indeed just water
But there was pesticide residue inside
They're getting old
Their bodies couldn't take the shock
They kept saying
You've always been their favorite
No, please, Mom and Dad
Sis, I was wrong
Tell the police to let me go
You hurt Mom and Dad
I'm not helping you anymore
Sis, Brother-in-law
I was wrong to treat you that way
I really learned my lesson
Please, let me go
An apology isn't enough
The ones who loved you unconditionally
Are in a coma because of you
No one's going to spoil you now
You must pay for your actions
Defendant Daniel, for the crime of poisoning
The facts are clear
The evidence is solid
According to the law
Sentenced to three years in prison
Fellow villagers
Lewes is now the richest man in the neighboring province
But he hasn't forgotten his roots
He provided money and technology
To lead us all to success
We've established a cooperative
It officially opens today
Let's welcome Mr. Lewes for the ribbon-cutting
If we all work hard
I believe our lives will get better and better